Hello friends, how are you?  I hope
you all are well.  Friends, if
you also use Paytm application and
friends, if you also
want to insure your bike through your Paytm application, then
friends, here I am going to tell you the complete process of how
you
can insure your bike through Paytm application.  Whether
you have a bike, a scooter or a bike or any of
your two wheeler vehicles, if
you want to get insurance done for any two wheeler, then
you can easily do it through Paytm application
and here you get all the
premium plans here, so
whatever plans you want to get done here, you have to
select them here and then you can easily make the
payment here,
so sitting at home online,
you can get your
bike insured here in just 5 to 10 minutes through Paytm application.
So friends, let me
start the video information.  Let me
tell you how you can get
your bike insurance and two
wheeler insurance done here through the Paytm application.
So friends, see here,
what do you have to do first to get your bike insured through Paytm application
?  First of all you have to open Paytm application.  When you
open the Paytm application,
friends, you have to come down here.  You have to
scroll down a little and
see friends, here you will see some tabs.
And look friends,
here you will see an insurance option.
So here you will
see the insurance.  So car
insurance will be visible here.  Health Insurance,
Accident Insurance and All
Insurance Products here.  So
here you have to click on the All Insurance tab.
Look, here
you have to tap on the All Insurance one.
When you click on All Insurance,
friends,
you will see that motor insurance appears here.   There
is car insurance, bike insurance,
taxi insurance, personal accident
cover, health insurance, all these are
included.  So here
you have to click on the bike insurance button.
Ok?  So
you will get bike insurance here.  So if
you click on this,
you will directly
come to the bike insurance page.  Okay friends?  So this is
your page for bike insurance.  Then it will open.
Now see friends, if you are
not able to find the bike insurance page here,
then you
can search on Paytm at the top here.  You have to search for
bike insurance here above.
When you search for bike insurance, you will directly
see the bike option here.  So
look, here you will
see an option for bike insurance.  So if
you click on bike insurance here,
you will directly reach the bike insurance
page.  Now what to
do here?  Look friends, what do you have to do here
?  First of all, you have to
enter your vehicle number here.  Whatever
two-wheeler you want to insure, you have to
enter its registration number here.
Ok?  So whatever is your bike's vehicle
number, whatever is your bike number, you have to
enter the bike's registration number here.
So you can enter your registration number
here.  If you do
not have a registration number, here
you will see the option Proceed without Two
Wheeler Number.  Ok?  So if you have
not got the number of your two wheeler yet and still
you want to get it insured here, then
click on this.
And what do you have to do here?
Search any brand.  So here first of all you have to choose the
name of your bike here.
Which company is it?  Is it from Hero Motorcop, Honda
, Bajaj, TVS or any
other bike.  So like this, for
example, if you have this Honda
car.  After that,
which one is your Honda?  There
is Honda Activa, there is Honda Activa 1, there is Honda CB
350.  Or whatever vehicle you have,
choose it here.  For example,
your letter is.  Avitor, here you can choose
which is the registration year
, in which year you bought the vehicle and
where is the vehicle from.  So, this is how
you have to fill this entire form here.
So this is the best.  If you
have a vehicle number, then
enter your vehicle number here.
For example, look
here, I will enter my vehicle number
here.  Look here
friends, I have entered my vehicle number here.
After entering the vehicle number,
you will see an option here: View Free
Course.  So you have to click on this.
When you click on the option of View Free Course, it will
tell you here
that it will tell you
which car you have here.  So friends,
you have to confirm here.  Like mine is
written here TVS Sports 100cc.
So whatever vehicle you have,
you can see it here and choose it.  If there are
incorrect details here, then
after entering the incorrect details,
you can enter your number again
here.  So down here
you will see the option Yes it's my
vehicle.  If this is your vehicle then
click on it.  Click on this button.
Now look friends, here you will
see all these options here.  About insurance,
how much is the insurance and what
things are included in it.  Now look friends,
here first of all you have to
search the policy type here.  After this,
the ID also has to be checked here and the filter
option has to be checked.  So these three four
options are most important.  So first of all let me
tell you.  First of all
you have to click on policy type and
here you will get comprehensive and third party.
So here
comprehensive means that everything
is covered and in third party only yours,
suppose if an accident happens, then
here God, if an accident happens, then
here only your third
party is covered.
So what happens in comprehensive,
everything is covered in comprehensive.  Your own damage
is also covered and the accidents
that happen are also covered up here.
After this, see friends,
IDV value comes here.  So
you have to click on IDV value.  So
friends, here in IDV value you
see three options.  He
shows best value, minimum comes and custom
comes.  So look friends, I will
recommend you here that if you
choose IDV value here in best value, then what happens here?
For example, suppose if your car etc. gets
lost or stolen, then here
you can get it at the best price.
So I will recommend you that
here you can choose the one with best value.
What will happen with this is that
you will get the highest IDV
here.  And if
after choosing IDV here, you feel that the
more you
increase your IDV in your premium here, the more your premium will
increase here.  Please keep one thing in
mind.  So if you want to
keep it minimum then you can do it minimum here.   If you want to do the
best value, you can do the best value.
So for now I have
minimized it and told you here.  Now
look here in Sorting and Filters,
you get all the options here.
Like here you
can check the premium from low to high, as if
you want to check
which is the lowest rate premium and then you can
choose in the range of low to high.   You
can choose from a range of high to high to low.  You can
choose here according to IDV.  You
can choose here according to IDV high to low.  Apart from this,
you can
get insurance here.
Insurance types are available here.  So
here you can do shorting according to this.
Okay friends?  Friends,
whatever is here, you
can choose the filters here.
Apart from this, you will get options here.
See, in Popular Ads, you can
also get zero debit advance
here and 24*7 roadside
assistance is also available here.  So I would
recommend you that those with zero debt can
choose here.  So apart from this,
friends, when you click on View All here,
you get many more
add-ons here.  Like
you get the invoice cover.  Apart from this,
personal accident cover is available here
, passenger cover is available here.
Apart from this, you can take all your arguments
here.  So I just have to
take zero depth here.  So I
selected the one with zero depth.  Now see
friends, insurance comes here.
Now see friends,
after choosing all these options here, see
friends, here you are
told about the insurance.  Like God is of number.
One belongs to Tata AIG.  There is a Tata Toko Eiffco
Toko one.  And here the
rates of all of them are shown here.  One is from ICC Lambd.
One is from Bajaj Reliance.  So see
friends, here you can choose according to your choice.
You see friends, if
I buy Tata Digit here, then
I am getting IDB value of ₹10,920 here.
And if I am buying Tata AIG then
here I am
getting IDV value of 17,000.  And here if I
take this then I am getting Rs 17,000 in it.
In ICC LBR I am getting IDV of Rs 15,000
and see friends, in this Bajaj Ali I am
getting IDV value of Rs 22,000.
Now look friends, I
recommend one thing to you that you should keep in mind here
that you should try to buy the one in
which you are
getting the highest IDV value here so that you get that much
value of your vehicle here.
If God forbid your car etc. gets
stolen then you will
get the same premium here.
So you can choose here according to your choice.
So see friends, I can
choose here according to me.  I will do it.
So look here
friends, I have chosen Tata AIG, in which the
premium is being told to me here, the
premium is being told to be ₹967 here.  So
my insurance policy is worth ₹967.  Now
I clicked here.  Now it will say Just a few more
details.  So this question is did the
ownership of the vehicle change in the last 12
months?  So here, that is, if you have
changed the ownership of the vehicle, then if you have done so, then
click on yes, if you have not done so, then
click on no and did you make a
claim, if you have taken any claim in the last
policy, then if you have taken it, then pay yes, if you have
not taken it, then pay no and there is
NCB, see friends, here there is non-
claim bonus, NCB means
non-claim bonus, so if you have taken any claim
in your recent balance in the last policy, then if
you have taken any claim for that, then
here you have to click on yes
and if you have
not taken any claim in the last policy, then you have to
click on no and here you have to
choose your value.  So I chose 50% here.
After this,
click on the proceed button.
When I click on the proceed button, see friends,
I have filled all these details here.
If you have made a claim, you
can click on Yes.  If the claim is not taken
then you can click on No.  After this,
look here friends, you will be
asked for KYC details here.  So
here your full name will come here.
Whatever your full name is on the RC,
it will appear here.  Here you
can choose your chosen document KYC, whichever document you want to choose.
For KYC, here
you are shown only one option, PAN card PAN number.
So here
you have to enter your PAN card number.
After this your date of birth appears below.
After this your address appears below.
And here you
can check check check here.  If you
also need personal accident cover.  If you need personal accident
cover, you can check it.  If you don't want it,
you can say no to it.  You can leave this.
So let me fill in all the details here and
tell you the next process.
Look friends, I have filled all the details here.
My
name has already appeared here.  PAN number has arrived here.
PAN Number: I have entered my PAN card
number here.  You also have to enter your PAN
card number here.  Here
you have to check your date of birth.
After that you have to check your address.
After filling all these details,
you have to click on the Review Other Details button.
After this,
friends, whatever insurance
policy you have here, it will be available to you today.  So
I have selected this Tata AIG one.
Selected the one with compensation.  IDV
value is here.  And your
vehicle number will appear here.
Your prying will come here.  It is without
GST.  Keep this in mind.  So after
applying GST here, you will have to
download the policy here.  So
here you can also download your policy brochure.
After this
you will get your personal details here.  So
your mobile number will appear here and your
email ID will appear here.  You
can check your email ID here because
your policy details come on your email ID only.
After this you have to come down.  You have to
come down and see friends,
here the details of your previous policy will appear
here.  If you
remember your previous policy number here, then
you can enter your previous policy number
here.  Look friends,
you have checked all these details here.
After this you have to
enter your previous policy number here.
So see, I have entered the previous policy number
here.  After this,
you have to click on the Proceed to Pay button and make the
payment here.  So let
me click on the Proceed to Pay button.
Now look friends, it will tell you please do not
refresh and press the back button.  So
you don't have to refresh here.  Don't even press the back button.
So here,
after coming to the next page,
you have to make your payment here.
After this, see friends, here it will
tell you to proceed with document
upload and here through two PAN card numbers,
your KYC will be told here.
So here my KYC is not being done through PAN number.
So I
click on the option above.  Proceed with
document upload.  So I clicked on it.
Now see friends, here you have to
enter address proof.  The
size of the file format has to be entered here and the file
format has to be entered here.  So
I clicked on this.  Now here it will tell
you how to get KYC done?
Here you want to do it through Aadhar card
or through driving license
or you
want to do it through passport.  Ok?  So here
if I do it through Aadhar card, then
here you have to make Aadhar card and
put the photo of your first page here and put the photo of the back page here.
If you look here friends,
you will get the option of driving license and
password here.
So I want to get it done through driving license.
So I
chose my driving license from here.  Now he is
telling me here to upload the front side.  So
here I have to take a photo and after
taking the photo, I have to upload the first photo of my driving license here.
So let me take my photo and
post it here.  So see friends, here
I have put my Aadhar and
driving license
photo here and
click on upload and verify document.
After this, see friends,
what is here is saying uploading your
documents.  Now look friends, it is
written here that you are almost done with
uploading your documents.  So here
it is telling you please wait for a few
seconds.  So let's wait here for some time.
So we will do all this.  Look
friends, after doing all this
you have to make your payment here.
To make payment, you
can also make payment through UPI here.  You
can also make payment through credit card or debit card.  So
you have to enter the UPI PIN and simply make the payment here.  Will make the
payment.  After making the payment,
you will get your policy number here and the
complete details of the policy will be sent to
your email here.
Whatever email address you enter here, the
details of your policy will come to your email here.  So
I'm not just doing insurance for now.
Because I will do the insurance
later.  So for now, I have
told you the entire process here as to what
you have to do.
Which options have to be selected here
and how do you have to do KYC etc. here.
When you complete all these options,
you will
get the payment option here.  After getting the payment option,
your policy will be sent to your email.
Okay friends?  So in this way, with the
help of Paytm application,
you can get your bike or two wheeler
insurance done here.  You
can get two wheeler insurance done here.
If you liked the video information then
please like and
share the video.  If you have any question,
query or suggestion, you
can ask by commenting below.
Thank you very much for watching the video.  Let's meet you
in the next video.  Till then keep speaking about
Bholenath of every continent.